<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
  <Leaders>
    <Row>
      <Type>LEADER_SHURELIA</Type>
      <Description>TXT_KEY_LEADER_SHURELIA</Description>
      <Civilopedia>TXT_KEY_LEADER_SHURELIA_PEDIA</Civilopedia>
      <CivilopediaTag>TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SHURELIA</CivilopediaTag>
      <ArtDefineTag>Shurelia_Scene.xml</ArtDefineTag>
      <VictoryCompetitiveness>6</VictoryCompetitiveness>
      <WonderCompetitiveness>7</WonderCompetitiveness>
      <MinorCivCompetitiveness>7</MinorCivCompetitiveness>
      <Boldness>3</Boldness>
      <DiploBalance>6</DiploBalance>
      <WarmongerHate>6</WarmongerHate>
      <WorkAgainstWillingness>0</WorkAgainstWillingness>
      <WorkWithWillingness>0</WorkWithWillingness>
      <DenounceWillingness>6</DenounceWillingness>
      <DoFWillingness>6</DoFWillingness>
      <Loyalty>6</Loyalty>
      <Neediness>6</Neediness>
      <Forgiveness>4</Forgiveness>
      <Chattiness>7</Chattiness>
      <Meanness>4</Meanness>
      <PortraitIndex>0</PortraitIndex>
      <IconAtlas>SHURELIA_LEADER_ATLAS</IconAtlas>
    </Row>
  </Leaders>

  <Leader_MajorCivApproachBiases>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <MajorCivApproachType>MAJOR_CIV_APPROACH_WAR</MajorCivApproachType>
      <Bias>4</Bias>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <MajorCivApproachType>MAJOR_CIV_APPROACH_HOSTILE</MajorCivApproachType>
      <Bias>5</Bias>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <MajorCivApproachType>MAJOR_CIV_APPROACH_DECEPTIVE</MajorCivApproachType>
      <Bias>7</Bias>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <MajorCivApproachType>MAJOR_CIV_APPROACH_GUARDED</MajorCivApproachType>
      <Bias>6</Bias>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <MajorCivApproachType>MAJOR_CIV_APPROACH_AFRAID</MajorCivApproachType>
      <Bias>5</Bias>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <MajorCivApproachType>MAJOR_CIV_APPROACH_FRIENDLY</MajorCivApproachType>
      <Bias>7</Bias>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <MajorCivApproachType>MAJOR_CIV_APPROACH_NEUTRAL</MajorCivApproachType>
      <Bias>5</Bias>
    </Row>
  </Leader_MajorCivApproachBiases>
  <Leader_MinorCivApproachBiases>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <MinorCivApproachType>MINOR_CIV_APPROACH_IGNORE</MinorCivApproachType>
      <Bias>4</Bias>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <MinorCivApproachType>MINOR_CIV_APPROACH_FRIENDLY</MinorCivApproachType>
      <Bias>6</Bias>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <MinorCivApproachType>MINOR_CIV_APPROACH_PROTECTIVE</MinorCivApproachType>
      <Bias>6</Bias>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <MinorCivApproachType>MINOR_CIV_APPROACH_CONQUEST</MinorCivApproachType>
      <Bias>5</Bias>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <MinorCivApproachType>MINOR_CIV_APPROACH_BULLY</MinorCivApproachType>
      <Bias>5</Bias>
    </Row>
  </Leader_MinorCivApproachBiases>
  <Leader_Flavors>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_OFFENSE</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>6</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_DEFENSE</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>6</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_CITY_DEFENSE</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>7</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_MILITARY_TRAINING</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_RECON</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_RANGED</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_MOBILE</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>6</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_NAVAL</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>3</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_NAVAL_RECON</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>3</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_NAVAL_GROWTH</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>3</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_NAVAL_TILE_IMPROVEMENT</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>3</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_AIR</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>3</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_EXPANSION</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>4</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_GROWTH</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>6</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_TILE_IMPROVEMENT</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>6</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_INFRASTRUCTURE</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>6</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_PRODUCTION</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>7</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_GOLD</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_SCIENCE</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>8</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_CULTURE</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>6</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_HAPPINESS</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>3</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_GREAT_PEOPLE</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>6</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_WONDER</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_RELIGION</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>6</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_DIPLOMACY</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_SPACESHIP</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>9</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_WATER_CONNECTION</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_NUKE</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>8</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_USE_NUKE</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>8</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_ESPIONAGE</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>6</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_ANTIAIR</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_AIR_CARRIER</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_ARCHAEOLOGY</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_I_LAND_TRADE_ROUTE</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_I_SEA_TRADE_ROUTE</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_I_TRADE_ORIGIN</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_I_TRADE_DESTINATION</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <FlavorType>FLAVOR_AIRLIFT</FlavorType>
      <Flavor>5</Flavor>
    </Row>
  </Leader_Flavors>
  <Leader_Traits>
    <Row>
      <LeaderType>LEADER_SHURELIA</LeaderType>
      <TraitType>TRAIT_MELODY_OF_ELEMIA</TraitType>
    </Row>
  </Leader_Traits>

  <Language_en_US>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_SHURELIA">
      <Text>Shurelia</Text>
      <Gender>feminine</Gender>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_SHURELIA_PEDIA">
      <Text><!-- Add Civilopedia text here --></Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SHURELIA_HEADING_1">
      <Text>Origins and Life Before Ar tonelico: Melody of Elemia</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SHURELIA_HEADING_2">
      <Text>Story in Ar tonelico: Melody of Elemia</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SHURELIA_HEADING_3">
      <Text>Role in Ar tonelico II: Melody of Metafalica</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SHURELIA_LIVED">
      <Text>3020 - ??? AD</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SHURELIA_NAME">
      <Text>EORIA_ANSUL_ARTONELICO</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SHURELIA_SUBTITLE">
      <Text>EORIA_ANSUL_ARTONELICO</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SHURELIA_TEXT_1">
      <Text>Shurelia is in fact a Reyvateil Origin, and the very first Reyvateil created in the world. The reason of the changing of her name is that her adoptive father, Eleno, had a daughter called Shurelia. The real Shurelia was killed in a security failure during the war between Sol Ciel and Sol Cluster some years before Eoria's birth, and after she was born, Eleno saw his daughter in Eoria. Because of that, he kept on calling Shurelia by the name of his dead daughter, Shurelia, eventually got so used to the name that she took it for herself. Shurelia liked so much the melody it played that Eleno, on her birthday, gave to her an orgel pendant as a present, and even if it couldn't diminish the pain from the Installs, Shurelia said herself that she would do for her beloved father. During this time, Shurelia was secluded in an special chamber of the Tower called the Parameno Room, singing to try to reduce the damage to the Tower, despite the unbearable pain she was feeling. Shurelia ended being very sad once she knew about Eleno's death, but she wasn't alone, given that Rovar, one of Eleno's direct subordinates stood by her side, and effectively turned into an older brother for her, and Neath, who was the direct subordinate for the president of Elemia, became her best friend. Shurelia ended becoming part of the Elemia Supreme Council, where she spoke of her plans for the construction of a new sound science system, the Silver Horn, for the sake of the people, but in exchange, she made everyone promise that it, and sound science in general would never be used for warfare again. This affected Shurelia so negatively that she even stood silent when Neath departed on a journey around the world, from which he would never come back. As a response, Shurelia showed the people the method for creating the Pureblood β-type Reyvateils, and they defeated the strange creatures. Shurelia was removed from the control of the Silver Horn, because the humans were planning to install a control system in it and make of Mir its controller, so they could completely control all of the Reyvateils in the world. The people appealed to Shurelia, and she called for a meeting for trying to return the peace to the world. This was just a ruse, since the people seized Shurelia as soon as she entered in the place where the meeting was supposed to take place, and after that, they sent her to an investigation center to apply the same process they had applied to Mir to strip her from her emotions and will. Mir rescued Shurelia from that awful fate, but the measures she took for doing so were so extreme, that Shurelia, extremely sad, disappointed and angered, declared war to Mir. Shurelia soon understood that she wouldn't be able to defeat Mir, given she was faster in her movements, and had much more power at her disposal. When Shurelia was about to give up, she remembered that Tastiella had offered her help to her, and she called Tastiella. To counter this, Tastiella and Shurelia designed and built, with the help of the Teru Tribe, the Crescent Chronicle, though this ended requiring the sacrifice of Tastiella for establishing the program that would seal Mir's virus form. The betrayals that Shurelia experienced during the war and the loss of so many friends led to her decision to not let herself feel any emotions again. Plus, how evil the people turned, the way they abused of the power of sounds and the Reyvateils, and the breaking of the promise they made were deciding factors for the final decision that Shurelia made after the war: she stripped the world away from the Hymmnos Extract songs, and completely banned the use of Sound Science in the world, as herself pleaded for it when the Covenant of Elemia was signed. Because of that, Shurelia herself had to banish him from Platina, though he would later return and once more try to revive Mir.</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SHURELIA_TEXT_2">
      <Text>
		  At the start of the game, she discovers the virus ELMA-DS breaking out from the Symphonic Reactor, and together with the Knights of Elemia, Lyner Barsett and Ayatane Michitaka, she tried to stop it from destroying Platina. She tried to analyze, and later on, combat the virus with Lyner and Ayatane backing her up they had to retreat after the virus performed Flip-Flop Conversion, making it impervious to any of their attacks. As it was a emergency, Shurelia entrusted Lyner with the sealed airship and the task of going down to the Wings of Horus to retrieve the Hymn Crystal Purger, since that was the only thing capable of cancelling ELMA-DS's Flip-Flop Conversion. She then gave to him a Brooch that projected a 3D image of the crystal to aid him in his search. She stayed in Platina to continue containing the viruses. Things end badly when she notices that the Mother Virus, Mir, is awake and plans to resume her plans to destroy mankind for the sake of making a perfect world only for Reyvateils, "Reyvateilia". As the first step in this plan, Mir sends an electrical discharge that causes one of the seven Hexagonal Plates to fall from the Musical Corridor, then knocks Shurelia unconscious. When Lyner finally returns with the Purger in his hands, Shurelia is containing ELMA-DS with the help of Ayatane and some other knights, but they retreat so Lyner and his party can take care of the virus. During the battle the virus breaks into Misha's mind, and Shurelia suggests that the entire party Dive to save her. In the middle of battling the virus which has taken over Misha's mind, Shurelia connects to the Tower and intervenes in order to separate Misha's consciousness from the viruses, then leaves the task of destroying the viruses to Lyner. Some of the candidates were Ayatane, Krusche and Lyner; Ayatane turned down the offer, since he wanted to continue protecting Shurelia, but Krusche, on the other hand agreed. Shurelia isn't seen again until after the Holy War incident. After all of that, Lyner and all of his friends reunited in the Platina Grand Hall where Shurelia thanked them for their brave efforts in saving Platina and recovering the Chronicle Key, but then she tripped and fell. While she was resting, Ayatane appeared, and showing his true identity and intentions, he helped Mir possess Shurelia's body. The viruses began pouring out of the Altar of Apostles once again, and when Lyner and the others went to investigate, they found Shurelia abducting Leard, sending him to the Prism Garden area of the Tower for "Knowing high level classified info". There, Leard informed them that Shurelia was possessed by Mir, and the only way to get Mir out of Shurelia's body was using an item called the FFT Divider. Lyner tried to reason with her to stop fighting, but she only laughed at him and attacked him. Misha tried to use the FFT Divider to sever the control that Mir had over Shurelia, but Mir summoned a guardian in response and Lyner figured out that they would need to fight with her to use the FFT Divider. After a grueling fight they finally managed to detach Mir from Shurelia's body, but Mir manifested as a monster. Lyner and the others fought and defeated her, but as Shurelia suspected, Mir revived, and when Mir said that she couldn't be killed unless the Tower was destroyed, Shurelia decided that it was time to use her last resort and shut down the Tower. Asking Lyner to remember all the experiences he had while traveling the world, and to please watch over the world in her place, she began singing the Suspend hymn. Mir was shocked at her actions, and Lyner was as well once he understood what the purpose of the song was, but Shurelia's only response was saying that she only wished to save the world. With nothing more left to do, Lyner's group took Shurelia with them and began climbing down the Tower. When they arrived back in Platina, and explained the situation to Leard he was shocked that things ended in that way, but he also was happy that the world wouldn't need an absolute administrator again, since these were Shurelia's wishes. Then everyone said their farewells and followed their own paths...[NEWLINE] Some months later, Shurelia was reawakened thanks to Aurica's singing of the Re=Nation hymn, which also restarted the Tower. Shurelia was initially angered because they ruined her plan of leaving the Tower inactive, which made Mir harmless. After she heard Lyner's reasons for these actions, she ended traveling with him because she wanted not only to find a better solution for everyone, but also to be able to feel the world again. Shurelia estimated that Mir had recovered around half of her power and told Leard that their only chance now was destroying Mir's body. Shurelia said that they didn't have time for riddles, but Lyner accepted Tastiella's challenge and her suggestion to travel around the world to seek the answer. First, they went to the Elemia Temple in the Falcon's Claw, where Shurelia explained to them about the temples that the Trio of Elemia had dedicated to them in the past, and how Mir was once worshipped in them as well, despite the cruel treatment she had received. They continued on to the Observatory to ask Mei Mei about Ayatane's whereabouts, and Shurelia was shocked when Mei Mei told them he was inside the Plasma Bell and planning to destroy it, because without the Bell, the Wings of Horus would be sent plummeting down into the Sea of Death. At this point, Shurelia began to reopen her heart to the people and show her feelings, revealing that because of all that had transpired during the last 700 years she had led a very hard life, and her immortality was also a very big burden for her. In the Plasma Bell, Shurelia told them the only thing they could do was stop the guardian of the Bell, the Child of Light, since Ayatane had already finished overwriting her programming with new orders: destroy the Plasma Bell. Shurelia warned everyone about the dangers of their next destination: the Silver Horn, because of the powerful Symphonic Energy barrier that was protecting it: the Voice of God. After crossing the Horn and arriving to the room where Mir was kept imprisoned up to the time of her rebellion, Shurelia recognized the place as the workshop where she used to make songs before Mir's birth. Shurelia was very sad after learning about all what that caused Mir to become like this, and told Lyner to help console her. After the final battle, Shurelia suggested to make a song with the intent of giving eternal peace to the world, and then, they began traveling around all of Sol Ciel to gather the feelings of the people.
	  </Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SHURELIA_TEXT_3">
      <Text>Shurelia first appeared near the end of the game, when Jakuri contacted her through Raki and the Binary Field of the Second Tower, seeking help for hacking the security systems of Sol Marta to gain access to its deepest area: the Ar Ciel Sphere, and defeat the usurper Goddess that was being a hindrance to the singing of Metafalica. She also appeared in Frelia's Cosmosphere as one of the spies of the syndicate, appearing first as a communicator robot for Kuroaki, and later on, showing her true form: a spy with the mission of locating and eliminating Miu. Shurelia later on scolds and calls Mir a cheater because she hacked the Cosmosphere's program to summon her virus monster form during a battle against her, but Mir simply shrugged it off, and defeated her. At the end of the Cosmosphere, she, together with Misha and Aurica, congratulates Croix for clearing the Cosmosphere, and give their services to him and Jakuri in the form of the Dual Song Phantasmagoria, in which the three of them sing EXEC_PHANTASMAGORIA/. to amplify the power of Jakuri's Ar tonelico Song Magic. An imitation of Shurelia singing Primal Word also appears whenever Jakuri sings her Cursing Aide Song Magic, in which a super-deform figure resembling her appears, and whenever she tries launching the song, she trips down and throws it at the party instead, increasing their chances to deal critical hits to the enemies.</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SHURELIA_TITLES_1">
      <Text>Wandering Tower Administrator</Text>
    </Row>
  </Language_en_US>
</GameData>
