<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 6/6/2014 1:44:41 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SAYAKA_EXOTIC">
			<Text>
				War Hymn
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SAYAKA_EXOTIC_HELP">
			<Text>
				Because you have Exotic influence over the landowner of the tile this Unit is on, it gains an additional [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]5%[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SAYAKA_FAMILIAR">
			<Text>
				War Melody
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SAYAKA_FAMILIAR_HELP">
			<Text>
				Because you have Familiar influence over the landowner of the tile this Unit is on, it gains an additional [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]10%[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SAYAKA_POPULAR">
			<Text>
				War Rondo
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SAYAKA_POPULAR_HELP">
			<Text>
				Because you have Popular influence over the landowner of the tile this Unit is on, it gains an additional [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]15%[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SAYAKA_INFLUENTIAL">
			<Text>
				War Symphony
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SAYAKA_INFLUENTIAL_HELP">
			<Text>
				Because you have Influential influence over the landowner of the tile this Unit is on, it gains an additional [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]20%[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SAYAKA_DOMINANT">
			<Text>
				War Orchestra
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SAYAKA_DOMINANT_HELP">
			<Text>
				Because you have Dominant influence over the landowner of the tile this Unit is on, it gains an additional [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]25%[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength!
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_PMMM_INCUBATOR">
			<Text>
				Incubator
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_PMMM_INCUBATOR_HELP">
			<Text>
				Incubators have a high withdrawal rate from combat and bonus defense vs. Ranged attacks, but if successfully melee attacked, their attacker heals back the damage taken.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_PMMM_HOMURA_TRAIT">
			<Text>
				All for Her Sake
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_PMMM_HOMURA_TRAIT_HELP">
			<Text>
				Homura Akemi may very well be the most stoic and determined Magical Girl ever born. When she has a goal in mind, nothing stops her from achieving it...not even the goal itself. She loses [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]3% less[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_PMMM_SOUL_GEM] Soul Gem per turn if she is injured or in a poor Mood (though she is still subject to the 1% minimum Corruption per Turn rule). Additionally, even if she does fall in battle or reaches 0% Soul Gem, she returns to the battlefield at an astounding [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]75%[ENDCOLOR] faster rate than other Leader Magical Girls.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>