<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 9/24/2014 1:11:06 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_GILGAMESH_FSN">
			<Text>
				Gilgamesh
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_NAME">
			<Text>
				Gilgamesh
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_TITLES_1">
			<Text>
				King of Heroes
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_TITLES_2">
			<Text>
				The Oldest King
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_SUBTITLE">
			<Text>
				Leader of Sumer
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_LIVED">
			<Text>
				c. 2500 BCE
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_HEADING_1">
			<Text>
				History
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_HEADING_2">
			<Text>
				Identity
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_HEADING_3">
			<Text>
				Early Years
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_HEADING_4">
			<Text>
				Friendship
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_HEADING_5">
			<Text>
				Immortality
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_TEXT_1">
			<Text>
				Gilgamesh, also known as Archer, is the Archer-class Servant of Tokiomi Tohsaka in the Fourth Holy Grail War of Fate/Zero. He later forms a new contract with Kirei Kotomine that lasts ten years later into the time of the Fifth Holy Grail War of Fate/stay night. He has an obsession with Saber during both stories.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_TEXT_2">
			<Text>
				Gilgamesh is the great half-god, half-human king born from the union between the King of Uruk, Lugalbanda, and goddess Rimat-Ninsun. He ruled the Sumerian city-state of Uruk, the capital city of ancient Mesopotamia in the B.C. era. He was an ultimate, transcendent being so divine as to be two thirds god and one third human, and no others in the world could match him. He was a despot possessing high divinity who believed he was invincible. He is not merely a legend, and is said to have actually existed and ruled during the Sumer Dynasty five thousand years ago. He was the King of Heroes who possessed all things in the world, whose tale is recorded in mankind's oldest epic poem, the Epic of Gilgamesh which portrays Gilgamesh as a hero, destined to be king and achieve great feats, who is driven to meet his destiny, facing challenges together with his best friend Enkidu.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]His title, King of Heroes, is not meant to call him a king who is a hero, but instead implies that he is the king over all heroes. He is mankind's oldest hero, the origin of all myths and model on which heroes are based, so his story is copied within the mythologies of all the countries of the world. The heroes of various myths are derived from his legend, so his Gate of Babylon possesses all of their Noble Phantasms. Though there are several heroes holding the title of "King", the King of Knights and King of Conquerors, he is the only one in all of heaven and earth crowned with the title of "King of All Heroes."
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_TEXT_3">
			<Text>
				Born with a body that was of the highest grade by mortal standards and knowledge reaching truth, Gilgamesh was born, designed, as king and the Keystone of Heaven between the rising humans and the fading gods. He was sent to censure the humans and bind the earth slowly leaving the Age of Gods. He was a being embodying the two life sets of life forms, with the blood of those who had ruled and the blood of those who would rule from thereon. He was to be the ultimate neutral party able to discern their respective failings, adjudicating from their respective positions. During his childhood, he loved the gods instead of humanity, but the gods created Enkidu at that time to punish the arrogant king.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Enkidu observed the young Gilgamesh, but could not understand the need to punish such an amiable, ideal king who was praised and lauded by his infatuated subjects. There could be no flaw that required correction, and the only problem was that he did not submit to the gods even if he did respect them. Enkidu was forced to admit that the gods had been correct as he watched the boy grow into a young man. Practicing absolutism, oppression, duress, levies, and the utmost decadence from self-interest, the people of the kingdom lamented the change, and even the gods were perplexed at the extent of the expected transformation.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The reason was simply that he had been born with the conclusion already drawn, existing independently as a being neither fully divine or human. He acquired the characteristics of both, so his field of vision reached even past what the gods were able to comprehend. His overwhelming power bred overwhelming isolation, but his strength of self kept him from abandoning his kingship or fleeing from the mission imposed upon him. Through revering the gods and loving humanity, he decided to follow the path to its conclusion by deposing the gods and loathing humanity.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_TEXT_4">
			<Text>
				Gilgamesh encountered Enkidu for the first time outside of the Temple of Uruk, who immediately stated that he would reprimand the King and rectify his arrogance. They entered a battle that spanned several days, and Gilgamesh was forced to use all his strength to match his transforming opponent. He was either angered or surprised at having found his equal for the first time, insulting Enkidu as a clod of mud. He was forced to draw out his treasures that had been carefully stored away, marking the first use of the Gate of Babylon as a weapon, and although it was a reluctant and forced humiliation at first, he eventually began to enjoy it and brought them out without regret.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He eventually emptied the vault, and Enkidu was left with only a tenth of his clay. Rather than continue, Gilgamesh let himself fall backwards onto his back while bursting with laughter, Enkidu following in suit. He remarked that there would only be once chance to strike for each of them, and without any means of defense, it would leave only two foolish corpses. Enkidu was never able to interpret if that meant it was a tie or if Gilgamesh wanted to make it so that there would only be one corpse. Enkidu asked, “Do you not regret the treasures you have spent?” to which he replied in a bright voice, “Why, if it’s someone I should use it on, then it’s not unthinkable to do him the favor."[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gilgamesh and Enkidu became close friends afterward, marking the one and only story of eternally unchanging worth in all the world. They worked side by side, and Gilgamesh noted that his vault started to become disordered after having begun utilizing weapons as projectiles, calling it a bad habit. Looking towards Humbaba, the guardian of the forest and beast of the gods, Gilgamesh decided to seek out and defeat it. They did so with their combined strength, but Enkidu was left confused by the action. It had not been an order from the gods, and it could not have been for his people who suffered under him.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gilgamesh told him that it was part of purging the evils of the world to protect Uruk, but Enkidu could not understand why he would care about those he tyrannized. Gilgamesh explained his way of protecting humanity, causing Enkidu to fully realize the source of his isolation. Enkidu stated that Gilgamesh took the path of observation, causing Gilgamesh to smile embarrassedly like in his childhood and speak of it. In response to his passion, Enkidu pledged himself as a tool to Gilgamesh afterward, but Gilgamesh reprimanded him, explaining to him that he was his friend. Enkidu believed it was the only time Gilgamesh had ever shown relief.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He became the greatest and richest king on Earth, who eventually acquired all the treasures of the world. Uruk became unprecedentedly prosperous, and Gilgamesh was considered so powerful that even the gods could not ignore his existence. One goddess, Ishtar the goddess of fertility, even fell in love with Gilgamesh and proposed marriage to the perfect king. He rejected her immediately because he knew her to be a witch who was unfaithful, cruel, and the corruptor of all men. She became furious, feeling that he had insulted her, and went to her father, the god Anu, to get revenge. She begged him to unleash the Bull of Heaven.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The unopposable beast of the gods caused seven years of starvation and destruction on the earth. Working together, they defeated it after binding it with the Chains of Heaven, causing the dark clouds covering the world to fade and saving the land from the flood. Ishtar's reputation was once again crushed, and her fury did not abate. She requested they be put to death for the sin of slaying a beast of the gods with the body of a human. Her request was granted, and Enkidu, created by the gods, was unable to defy the decree.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He slowly weakened and was returned to clay, as Gilgamesh desperately held on to the crumbling clod in his arms. He was angered by this, believing that he was the one who deserved retribution should it be required. Enkidu attempted to assuage him by tell Gilgamesh that he was only one of the many treasures in Gilgamesh's collection, that he would find countless more greater than him in time. Gilgamesh instead declared, “You do have worth. You alone have this worth. I hereby declare. In all this world, only one shall be my friend. Thus---not for all eternity shall his worth ever change.” Enkidu returned to his original state afterward, leaving nothing behind but Gilgamesh's thunderous cry.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_GILGAMESH_FSN_TEXT_5">
			<Text>
				Up until that point, Gilgamesh had lived by his own standards, collecting riches, bedding women, fighting with his friend, and purging the earth of banes. Enkidu returning to dust, meeting death, greatly changed his views. Death had never inspired grief or fear in him until that moment, and it had never once even been in his mind though he knew that it awaited all. Seeing the one who held equal power to him perish before his eyes let him register the true reality of death for the first time. Falling into depression and with his vigor gone, he sought out the Herb of Immortality, a spirit herb of perpetual youth and eternal life.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He had known of it even before Enkidu's passing, and had planned to obtain it eventually in order to complete his collection. With a reason to search for it, he left for the underworld, Kigal. He sought out he sage, Utnapishtim, who had lived since placing a large amount of animals upon an ark before the coming of a deluge that assailed the earth. He was said to have been the only one of the earth escape from death and live until the present.[1] He loathed and feared the death that took away his friend, making him frightened for his own life for the first time since birth. He went on his journey, that he later called a farce, that lasted the same amount of time as he had lived up until that point.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He wandered the wilderness for decades as described in the epic, "grovelling along pathetically" while thinking nothing other than not wanting to die. He had the same motive as all humans, as not even a child of the gods was any different when faced with death. With "idiocy exceeding that of humans", he continued to attempt to overcome death, flinging aside the pride, authority, and power of the king, without knowing a purpose to do so or someone for whom to do it. His fear of death was one of the reasons for his actions, but he also loathed death because he could not forgive himself for abandoning his role of observing the future.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He eventually reached the realm of the dead, and found that upon meeting with Utnapishtim that his form of immortality was not special at all. Utnapishtim had gained longevity by joining the ranks of the gods, half becoming a plant in the process. He rejected such an immortality because he had to be immortal with the desires of a human still intact, rather than simply living eternally in a body with no appetition. He had simply planned to leave the underworld and return to Uruk to bring his vault to completion, but Utnapishtim, having grown doubtful of having his way of existence rejected or possibly wanting to condemn one who had denied immortality from the gods to the same existence, told Gilgamesh a secret.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He told Gilgamesh a method of becoming immortal without seeking the mercy of the gods, the root of a herb that grew in the deep. Though he would not consume it himself, as he would only become a plant, he collected it as a rare treasure to decorate his vault. Stopping within the deep, he jarred the herb and returned above ground. Unable to put words to his state of mind at the time, there was some part of him that was hopeful even though he declared that there was no need of immortality modeled on the gods. He smiled at his accomplishment upon returning above ground, believing that he could overthrow death and avenge his friend.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]With the ability to rise above the "death" that had taken even Enkidu, the voices and acclaim of the people of Uruk would have reached unprecedented level upon returning with immortality. Describing himself as being in the "rashness of youth", vanity soon followed and he became bother by his ragged state to which he had not spared a single thought until that moment. He wished to cleanse himself before returning to Uruk to test the fruits of his labor in perfect condition, so he rested at a spring close by to recover from the fatigue accumulated over decades of searching. He experienced a certain feeling at that point that he believed to be his first true feeling of joy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]As the water healed him, he felt a peacefulness like being released from a prolonged malaise in both body and mind. It was the first time he had been so ecstatic about any of his accomplishments because the act of amassing treasures is like an instinct similar to breathing that does not bring joy to him. The action of obtaining immortality was the first time he was thankful for being born into the world because, despite claiming to have the perspective of humans, he believed he was not human until that moment. He felt free from everything, no doubts, fears, fixations, or duties. Overwhelmed by the sensation of omnipotence, he describes the feeling as élan vital, the reward of his self desire and the belief that he could do as he pleased with that joy for all eternity.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]It was then that his carelessness caused it to be snatched away from him, brought down by the desires, simple appetition of “hunger”, of a serpent that crawled the wilds. The snake with an empty stomach was drawn by the herb's smell, and although a panicked Gilgamesh emerged from the spring, it was too late. The snake gained the property of shedding, having been the restoration of youth instead of immortality, and all that was left was its shed skin. He then was struck with laughter at the event, the absurdity of the conclusion in all he stood to gain and all he took pride in being "naught." He laughed at his own foolishness until his sides ached.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Though it was not that he was unable to obtain anything, he understood that his sole reward was that not one thing would remain for him. The fulfillment in life and joy that he obtained for the first time vanished instantly, causing him to realize that was the nature of the human world. Realizing that immortality was unnecessary to his duty, he had been born as a human at that moment and died as a human after learning of joy. Though he had been "complete since birth", he also had his times of inexperience. Taking nearly the entirety of his life to complete his development, he reached physical maturity in the time with Enkidu and mental maturity at that moment, marking the end of his youth.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Having laughed away the theft, the sun had risen, and smiling at the fleeting moment of human joy, he returned to Uruk. Marking the end of his adventures, he governed Uruk as the ruler of heroes and brought it to completion. He later also returned to the deep to retrieve the herb once more simply to complete his collection and for the off-chance he would ever be in a situation he could only tolerate as a child. Though he was still severe, he ruled Uruk quietly, entrusting it to the next king before going to his eternal rest without telling the whereabouts of the herb. He became humanity’s most ancient hero and the illustrious king who was the first in this world to have “become a story."[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]It is said that the snake begins its life again in a new body after shedding its skin because it stole Gilgamesh's medicine and drank it. The way snakes went about their life appeared to the ancient people as a kind of perpetual youth and eternal life that was not available to humans. The skin shed by the first snake in the world in ancient times was later fossilized and remained in existence for countless eons before being used as a catalyst by Tohsaka Tokiomi to summon Gilgamesh as Archer in the Fourth Holy Grail War.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_DAWN_GILGAMESH_FSN_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Is there any praise which cannot be said about you, Gilgamesh, the almighty King of Heroes? The gods created you as a mixture of divinity and humanity, and you are a paragon of both. You are unquestionably the greatest ruler who ever lived, ruling over the first and most prosperous human civilization of Sumer. Despite -- no, because of your selfishness and greed, you built Uruk and its surroundings into the greatest civilization in the world. No Civilization which followed could even come close to its majesty. You amassed so many treasures that they would become the basis for all of the legends which followed your rule. You even came very near to obtaining immortality, until it was stolen by the snake.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Invincible King of Heroes, the world begs you once more for the privilege of having you rule. A world full of treasures lays ripe for the taking before you! There is no need to ask if you can build a civilization that can stand the test of time -- it is as guaranteed as the sunrise!
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_1">
			<Text>Uruk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_2">
			<Text>Eridu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_3">
			<Text>Kish</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_4">
			<Text>Lagash</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_5">
			<Text>Ur</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_6">
			<Text>Nibru</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_7">
			<Text>Bad-Tibira</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_8">
			<Text>Zimbir</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_9">
			<Text>Shuruppak</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_10">
			<Text>Umma</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_11">
			<Text>Larsa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_12">
			<Text>Isin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_13">
			<Text>Girsu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_14">
			<Text>Adab</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_15">
			<Text>Zabalam</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_16">
			<Text>Akshak</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_17">
			<Text>Larak</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_18">
			<Text>Kisiga</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_19">
			<Text>Nina</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_20">
			<Text>Dilbat</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_21">
			<Text>Kutu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_22">
			<Text>Marad</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_23">
			<Text>Enegi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_24">
			<Text>Abu Salabikh</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_25">
			<Text>Ki-an</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_26">
			<Text>Pazurish-Dagan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_27">
			<Text>Dabrum-Zabalam</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_28">
			<Text>Kissura</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_29">
			<Text>Kutallu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_30">
			<Text>Nagsu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_31">
			<Text>Kesh</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_32">
			<Text>Aratta</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_33">
			<Text>Der</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_34">
			<Text>Hamazi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_35">
			<Text>Apisada</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_36">
			<Text>Jemdet Nasr</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_37">
			<Text>Ubaid</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_SUMER_FSN_ADJECTIVE">
			<Text>Sumerian</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_SUMER_FSN_DESC">
			<Text>Sumerian Empire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_SUMER_FSN_SHORT_DESC">
			<Text>Sumer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_0">
			<Text>Kirei</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_1">
			<Text>Enkidu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_2">
			<Text>Amar-sin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_3">
			<Text>Ur-Nammu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_4">
			<Text>Eannatum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_5">
			<Text>Ninbanda</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_6">
			<Text>Ashusikildigir</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_7">
			<Text>Shulgi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_8">
			<Text>Aanepada</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_SUMER_FSN_9">
			<Text>Inanna</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_SUMER_FSN_TITLE">
			<Text>Sumer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_SUMER_FSN_HEADING_1">
			<Text>History</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_SUMER_FSN_TEXT_1">
			<Text>
				Sumer was an ancient civilization and historical region in southern Mesopotamia, modern Iraq, during the Chalcolithic and Early Bronze Age. Although the earliest historical records in the region do not go back much further than ca. 2900 BC, modern historians have asserted that Sumer was first settled between ca. 4500 and 4000 BC by a non-Semitic people who may or may not have spoken the Sumerian language (pointing to the names of cities, rivers, basic occupations, etc. as evidence). These conjectured, prehistoric people are now called "proto-Euphrateans" or "Ubaidians", and are theorized to have evolved from the Samarra culture of northern Mesopotamia (Assyria). The Ubaidians were the first civilizing force in Sumer, draining the marshes for agriculture, developing trade, and establishing industries, including weaving, leatherwork, metalwork, masonry, and pottery. However, some scholars such as Piotr Michalowski and Gerd Steiner, contest the idea of a Proto-Euphratean language or one substrate language.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Sumerian civilization took form in the Uruk period (4th millennium BC), continuing into the Jemdat Nasr and Early Dynastic periods. During the third millennium BC, a close cultural symbiosis developed between the Sumerians (who spoke a Language Isolate) and the Semitic Akkadian speakers, which included widespread bilingualism. The influence of Sumerian on Akkadian (and vice versa) is evident in all areas, from lexical borrowing on a massive scale, to syntactic, morphological, and phonological convergence. This has prompted scholars to refer to Sumerian and Akkadian in the third millennium as a sprachbund. Sumer was conquered by the Semitic-speaking kings of the Akkadian Empire around 2270 BC, but Sumerian continued as a sacred language. Native Sumerian rule re-emerged for about a century in the Third Dynasty of Ur of the 21st to 20th centuries BC, but Akkadian also remained in use. The Sumerian city of Eridu, on the coast of the Persian Gulf, was the world's first city, where three separate cultures fused - that of peasant Ubaidian farmers, living in mud-brick huts and practicing irrigation; that of mobile nomadic Semitic pastoralists living in black tents and following herds of sheep and goats; and that of fisher folk, living in reed huts in the marshlands, who may have been the ancestors of the Sumerians.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The surplus of storable food created by this economy allowed the population of this region to settle in one place, instead of migrating as hunter gatherers. It also allowed for a much greater population density, and in turn required an extensive labour force and division of labour with many specialised arts and crafts. Sumer was also the site of early development of writing, progressing from a stage of proto-writing in the mid 4th millennium BC to writing proper in the third millennium.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZIGGURAT_FSN">
			<Text>
				Ziggurat
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZIGGURAT_FSN_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Ziggurats were massive structures built in the ancient Mesopotamian valley and western Iranian plateau, having the form of a terraced step pyramid of successively receding stories or levels. Notable ziggurats include the Great Ziggurat of Ur near Nasiriyah, Iraq; the Ziggurat of Aqar Quf near Baghdad, Iraq; the now destroyed Etemenanki in Babylon (possibly the inspiration behind the biblical story of the Tower of Babel); Chogha Zanbil in Khūzestān, Iran; and Sialk near Kashan, Iran.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]While they were largely considered to be both religious and political in function, in this version of Sumer, Gilgamesh has made it purely the latter. Gilgamesh is two-thirds God himself, but he has openly denounced the Gods and despises them, so his Divinity has been lowered and he greatly discourages his populace from their worship.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZIGGURAT_FSN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Ziggurat is the Unique Building for Sumer, replacing the Shrine. Unlike the Shrine it replaces, it provides no [ICON_PEACE] Faith -- which is not an issue, as Gilgamesh's Faith yields are negated anyway. However, it does provide +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.
			</Text>
		</Row>


		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GILGAMESH_VAULT">
			<Text>
				Vault of the Golden Capital
			</Text>
			<Gender>
				neuter:the
			</Gender>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GILGAMESH_VAULT_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Gilgamesh collected and stored away samples of all the technology that was developed during his age, making his favorite phrase, "I collected all the treasures of the earth", not an exaggeration or metaphor. The treasury contains all of the treasures of the world that he collected during his life, from the finest wine and golden drinking cups to divine mysteries from nearly every legend. As anything can be found within the vault, the amount of wealth within exceeds even his own knowledge. The desires of ancient humans were similar to those of the current age, so their technology, bolstered by the magical energy being alive and well, was not inferior to that of the modern age. The "Instruments of Hope" that people dreamed of were all realized, and because every single case was requisitioned by the King's hand, his collection is even furnished with airplanes and submarines. It also contains all of the original bases for all intellectual properties produced by mankind that originated in his kingdom, making board games and the works of the Library of Alexandria no more than imitations.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GILGAMESH_VAULT_HELP">
			<Text>
				This replacement for the East India Company may only be constructed by Sumer. Must have built a Market in all Cities. The cost goes up the more cities there are in the empire. Unlike the East India Company, it provides no bonuses to Trade Route income. However, it has 4 slots for Great Works of Art or Artifacts. If the Theming Bonus for this building is earned, it will reduce Unit Maintenance by 33% and will reduce the cost of purchasing items with Gold by 15%.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GILGAMESH_VAULT_HELP_CBP">
			<Text>
				This replacement for the East India Company may only be constructed by Sumer. Must have built a Market in the city. The cost goes up the more cities there are in the empire. Unlike the East India Company, it provides no bonuses to Trade Route income. However, it has 4 slots for Great Works of Art or Artifacts. If the Theming Bonus for this building is earned, it will reduce Unit Maintenance by 33% and will reduce the cost of purchasing items with Gold by 15%. Requires a national population of at least 45 before it can be constructed.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GILGAMESH_VAULT_THEMING">
			<Text>
				All the Treasures of the World
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GILGAMESH_VAULT_THEMING_HELP">
			<Text>
				To maximize your theming bonus, make sure all slots are filled with Artifacts from different Civilizations and different Eras.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TRAIT_GATE_OF_BABYLON">
			<Text>
				May build any Unique Unit in the game. (Civilian units are excluded.) Units require twice as much experience to level up. All [ICON_PEACE] Faith earned is converted to [ICON_GOLD] Gold.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TRAIT_GATE_OF_BABYLON_SHORT">
			<Text>
				Gate of Babylon
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITYSTATE_MISAKI">
			<Text>
				Misaki
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITYSTATE_MISAKI_ADJ">
			<Text>
				Misakian
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITYSTATE_MISAKI_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Misaki Town is the town where the events Tsukihime, Kagetsu Tohya, Melty Blood series, and Mahou Tsukai no Yoru takes place in, and the town also appears in Kara no Kyoukai. 
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_ALERT_GILGAMESH_FAITH_CONVERTED_TO_GOLD">
			<Text>
				{1_Num} [ICON_PEACE] Faith was converted directly to [ICON_GOLD] Gold.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>